thehdroom.com 2013-04-30

# 

**TheHDRoom Privacy Policy**

By creating an HDR User Account, you agree to and accept all of the following Terms and Conditions contained in the Privacy Policy below. 

In compliance with The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and due to the nature of material presented on this site, you must be over the age of 17 to create an account and actively participate on the site through product reviews, forum messages and all other means of interaction. 

TheHDRoom will not be held responsible for any damages incurred as a result of content which you submit or post to TheHDRoom website. 

Your User Account can be terminated at any time at the sole discretion of TheHDRoom staff. 

Any personal information such as name, mailing address and E-Mail address collected during the registration process is not distributed by TheHDRoom. No personal information is ever re-sold to a third party vendor. 

Any product reviews or site interaction you provide may be used for the purpose of attracting visitors, advertisers, and partners to TheHDRoom. 

The views and opinions expressed by visitors in the HDR Forums are in no way endorsed or sponsored by TheHDRoom or their staff. TheHDRoom reserves the right to edit or delete any post at its discretion at any time. While freedom of speech is practiced in TheHDRoom, any blatant attacks deemed harmful to other members, consistent posting of pornographic material, or persistent spamming may result in immediate termination of your account. 

***Cookies*** 

TheHDRoom (HDR) uses cookies in order to identify users whom are logged into the site and keep them logged in when they return for a new session. No further use of cookies is used. 

***Advertising*** 

Zboos LLC may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

***Disclosure*** 

TheHDRoom openly volunteers its practices of collecting and applying information submitted by its registered membership base. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or about any other aspect of TheHDRoom and any associated practices please contact us at support@TheHDRoom.com 

_Last Updated: February 3, 2011_
